welcomebabyhome.com 2015-06-11

# Welcome Baby Home - Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for [www.welcomebabyhome.com](http://www.welcomebabyhome.com/). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

**Your Access to and Control over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email at 

[  
customerservice@welcomebabyhome.com](mailto:customerservice@welcomebabyhome.com)

\- See what data we have about you, if any.   
\- Change/correct any data we have about you.  
\- Have us delete any data we have about you.   
\- Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

**Log Files**

OEM may use Internet Provider (IP) addresses and IDs to analyze trends, administer the welcomebabyhome.com web site, track users movement to prevent abuse, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use by OEM.OEM logs IP addresses and user browser types for statistical and systems administration purposes only. These logs are analyzed to determine user interest in the various areas of our site, to identify system performance or problem areas, and to improve the value of the materials available on the web site. 

**Communication**

OEM will periodically communicate via email and other means with individuals who have registered at the site for our services. Registering to participate or purchase products from the welcomebabyhome.com web site is interpreted as "opting in" to agree to receive information from OEM. Individuals who have registered for our services and who wish to remove themselves from lists for future communications can email us at 

• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. 

• Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the 

[Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES **

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to third party websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own terms and privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these sites and their terms and policies. 

**Tell-A-Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about OEM products & services, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. The welcomebabyhome.com web site will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. OEM does not store this information after sending the one-time email. 

**Legal Information**

We reserve the right to inform any applicable authority should we believe that any payment has been made, or attempted to be made using fraudulent details or methods. We further reserve the right to disclose any information necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation or reasonable legal request. If you have any further queries regarding your rights to privacy, please contact us directly 

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email at**

Thank you
